free-strip-games.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy and terms | Free-Strip-Games.com

Follow us!

Best Friends

##  What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your e-mail address, name and surname. You may, however, visit the public area of our site anonymously.

##  What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you).
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs).
  * To process transactions: 

> Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
  * To send periodic emails: 

> The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.

##  Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

##  Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

##  Comments and posts

We have the right to delete any comments posted on our website. Any illegal or offensive comment will be immediately deleted and its author banned from our forums.

##  Account

It is strictly forbidden to post one's credentials on a third-party website or on our website. Doing so will result in a permanent ban from our website.

##  Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

##  Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.

##  Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on 2016-01-27.

##  Contacting us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using this email:

More Friends
